<resources>
    <string name="app_name">R47</string>
    <string name="about_gpl_license_title">View GNU GPL v3 Notice</string>
    <string name="about_gpl_license_summary">Shows the packaged GPL v3 text and source-delivery guidance for this build</string>
    <string name="about_android_source_title">View Android Source Repository</string>
    <string name="about_android_source_summary">Public source repository for this Android build</string>
    <string name="about_repo_notices_title">View Bundled Native and Vendored Notices</string>
    <string name="about_repo_notices_summary">Shows repo-owned notices for vendored or native surfaces that do not come from Maven metadata</string>
    <string name="about_android_library_licenses_title">View Android Library Notices</string>
    <string name="about_android_library_licenses_summary">Shows notices collected from Android runtime dependency POM metadata</string>
    <string name="about_spdx_inventory_title">View SPDX Inventory</string>
    <string name="about_spdx_inventory_summary">Shows the packaged machine-readable third-party inventory</string>
    <string name="about_upstream_project_title">Visit Upstream C47 Project Page</string>
    <string name="lcd_luminance_title">LCD Luminance</string>
    <string name="lcd_luminance_summary">Adjust the LCD tone while preserving the selected hue</string>
    <string name="gpl_license_missing_message">This build could not read the packaged GNU GPL text from the APK.</string>
    <string name="repo_notice_catalog_title">Bundled Native and Vendored Notices</string>
    <string name="repo_notice_catalog_missing_message">This build could not read the packaged repo notice index from the APK.</string>
    <string name="repo_notice_asset_missing_message">This build could not read the selected packaged notice from the APK.</string>
    <string name="repo_notice_asset_fallback_title">Packaged Notice</string>
    <string name="about_gpl_license_intro">R47 Android is licensed under the GNU General Public License, version 3.

This program comes with ABSOLUTELY NO WARRANTY.

A verbatim copy of the GPL is packaged in this APK below.

Distributors of APKs must also provide the exact corresponding source for the build they ship. Use the Android source repository entry in Settings to reach the public Android fork for this build. The packaged SOURCE manifest also records the synchronized upstream core revision when the build provides one.</string>
    <string name="gpl_license_dialog_close">Close</string>
</resources>
